<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PathPulse</string>

    <string name="explorer">Explorer</string>
    <string name="stats">Stats</string>
    <string name="memories">Memories</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>

    <string name="visited_countries">Visited Countries</string>
    <string name="last_visited_country">Last visited country</string>

    <string name="describe_your_memory">Describe your memory</string>
    <string name="my_journey_to">My journey to…</string>
    <string name="rate_your_journey">Rate your journey</string>
    <string name="add_in_collection">ADD IN COLLECTION</string>
    <string name="find_your_country">Find country</string>


    <string name="uae_TOP">UNITED ARAB EMIRATES</string>
    <string name="uae_desc">The United Arab Emirates (UAE) is a country in the Middle East, located on the Arabian Peninsula. It consists of seven emirates, including Abu Dhabi (the capital) and Dubai. Known for its modern architecture, luxury tourism, and rapid development, the UAE is a global business hub. It has a rich cultural heritage, strong economy based on oil, trade, and tourism, and is known for landmarks like the Burj Khalifa and Palm Jumeirah.</string>
    <string name="usa_TOP">UNITED STATES OF AMERICA</string>
    <string name="usa_desc">The United States is a federal republic in North America made up of 50 states and the District of Columbia. Spanning roughly 9.8 million km²—from the Arctic expanses of Alaska to the sun‑drenched beaches of Florida and Hawaii—it encompasses nearly every climate zone on Earth. As the world’s largest economy (about $27 trillion nominal GDP), it leads in technology, entertainment, and finance. A true cultural melting pot shaped by centuries of immigration, the U.S. is famed for landmarks such as the Grand Canyon, Yellowstone National Park, and the Statue of Liberty.</string>
    <string name="france_TOP">FRANCE</string>
    <string name="france_desc">France is a semi‑presidential republic in Western Europe, its mainland covering some 551,000 km²—making it the largest country in the EU—plus five overseas regions. From the art‐filled streets of Paris (its capital and culinary heart) to the lavender fields of Provence and the Alpine peaks of Chamonix, it offers a dazzling array of landscapes. With a nominal GDP near $3 trillion, France is renowned for luxury fashion, gourmet cuisine, and world‑class wine. Home to over 40 UNESCO World Heritage Sites—like Mont‑Saint‑Michel, the Palace of Versailles, and the medieval city of Carcassonne—it stands as a global beacon of art, history, and tradition.</string>
    <string name="finland_TOP">FINLAND</string>
    <string name="finland_desc">Finland is a Nordic republic in Northern Europe, known for its vast boreal forests, some 188,000 lakes, and the Northern Lights dancing over Lapland in winter. With a strong welfare state and world‑renowned education system, it consistently ranks among the happiest and most prosperous nations. Helsinki, its coastal capital, showcases sleek design and innovative architecture alongside vibrant café culture. Finland’s advanced technology sector—from Nokia to global gaming studios—thrives amid a tradition of saunas and outdoor living. The country’s Midnight Sun in summer and aurora‑lit skies in winter offer a year‑round showcase of natural wonder.</string>
    <string name="norway_TOP">NORWAY</string>
    <string name="norway_desc">Norway is a constitutional monarchy on the western edge of the Scandinavian Peninsula, famed for its dramatic fjords, glacier‑carved valleys, and coastal archipelagos. Its high‑income mixed economy centers on petroleum, fishing, and shipping, underpinned by a comprehensive social‑welfare model. Oslo, the capital, blends modernist architecture with lush green spaces and the striking Opera House at the waterfront. In Northern Norway, visitors chase the Midnight Sun in summer and the aurora borealis in winter. A legacy of Viking heritage and stave churches dot the countryside, making Norway a land of both deep history and cutting‑edge sustainability.</string>
    <string name="uk_TOP">UNITED KINGDOM</string>
    <string name="uk_desc">The United Kingdom is a sovereign state off northwestern Europe, uniting England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland under a constitutional monarchy and parliamentary democracy. London—the capital—is a global financial center, famed for landmarks like the Tower of London, Buckingham Palace, and the West End theatre district. Across rolling English countryside, Scottish Highlands, Welsh coastlines, and Northern Irish lakes, the UK offers a tapestry of landscapes and regional traditions. Its £2.7 trillion economy is driven by services, manufacturing, and creative industries. With over 30 UNESCO World Heritage Sites—from Stonehenge to the historic city of Bath—the UK’s blend of ancient heritage and modern innovation captivates visitors worldwide.</string>
    <string name="spain_TOP">SPAIN</string>
    <string name="spain_desc">Spain is a parliamentary constitutional monarchy occupying most of the Iberian Peninsula, plus the Balearic and Canary Islands. Covering about 506,000 km² from the Pyrenees to the Atlantic shore, it boasts diverse landscapes—from sun‑baked beaches and rolling vineyards to snow‑capped mountains. With a nominal GDP around €1.4 trillion, Spain’s economy leans heavily on tourism, manufacturing, and renewable energy. Spanish culture dazzles through flamenco dance, world‑famous festivals like La Tomatina and Running of the Bulls, and a rich culinary scene of tapas, paella, and regional wines. Home to 49 UNESCO World Heritage Sites—such as the Alhambra, Sagrada Família, and the medieval city of Toledo—Spain is an open‑air gallery of art, history, and architecture.</string>
    <string name="italy_TOP">ITALY</string>
    <string name="italy_desc">Italy is a parliamentary republic in Southern Europe, comprising the boot‑shaped peninsula plus Sicily and Sardinia. Spanning roughly 301,000 km² from the Alpine foothills to the Mediterranean coast, it features dramatic coastlines, rolling hills, and Alpine peaks. As the world’s eighth‑largest economy (around €2.1 trillion), Italy leads in luxury fashion, automotive design, and artisanal food and wine production. Renowned as the birthplace of the Renaissance, it offers masterpieces from the canals of Venice and the galleries of Florence to Rome’s ancient Colosseum. Boasting 58 UNESCO World Heritage Sites—the highest count worldwide—Italy is a vibrant tapestry of art, architecture, and culinary heritage.</string>
    <string name="morocco_TOP">MOROCCO</string>
    <string name="morocco_desc">Morocco sits at the crossroads of Europe and Africa, spanning the Mediterranean and Atlantic coasts and encompassing part of the Sahara Desert. A constitutional monarchy, its economy blends traditional crafts—such as ceramics and leatherwork—with modern sectors like phosphate mining and tourism. The imperial cities of Marrakech, Fès, Rabat, and Meknès showcase ornate palaces, bustling souks, and centuries‑old madrasas. Atlas Mountains treks, Sahara camel caravans, and Andalusian‑inspired riads make Morocco an intoxicating fusion of Arab, Berber, and European influences.</string>

    <string name="widget_name">Travel Progress Bar</string>

</resources>